instantbannercreator.com 2019-03-03

# Privacy Policy

                        Privacy Policy
Welcome to themembershipscript.com (the "Site").
We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site,
especially when conducting business. This statement governs our
privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site ("Visitors") who
visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact
business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by
themembershipscript.com (collectively, "Services") ("Authorized
Customers").
Personally Identifiable Information
refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify,
contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains,
including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax
number, email address, financial profiles, social security number, and
credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not
include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without
identification of the individual user) or demographic information not
connected to an identified individual.
What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?
We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors.
We collect the following additional information from our Authorized
Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email
addresses of Authorized Customers, the nature and size of the
business, and the nature and size of the advertising inventory that the
Authorized Customer intends to purchase or sell.

What organizations are collecting the information?
In addition to our direct collection of information, our third party
service vendors (such as credit card companies, clearinghouses and
banks) who may provide such services as credit, insurance, and
escrow services may collect this information from our Visitors and
Authorized Customers. We do not control how these third parties use
such information, but we do ask them to disclose how they use
personal information provided to them from Visitors and Authorized
Customers. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act
solely as links in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use
the information given to them.
How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?
We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to
make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfil buying and selling
requests on the Site. We may email Visitors and Authorized
Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on
the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We
may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors
and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to
provide requested information.
With whom may the information be shared?
Personally Identifiable Information about Authorized Customers may
be shared with other Authorized Customers who wish to evaluate
potential transactions with other Authorized Customers. We may
share aggregated information about our Visitors, including the
demographics of our Visitors and Authorized Customers, with our
affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the

opportunity to "opt out" of receiving information or being contacted by
us or by any agency acting on our behalf.
How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?
Personally Identifiable Information collected by
themembershipscript.com is securely stored and is not accessible to
third parties or employees of themembershipscript.com except for use
as indicated above.
What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and
distribution of the information?
Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving updates,
product information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors
and affiliated agencies by using the unsubscribe link in our emails, or
you may login to your members account profile and turn off email
notifications directly from your dashboard
Are Cookies Used on the Site?
Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain
information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they
select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our
Authorized Customers. For example, if an Authorized Customer is
logged on and the site is unused for more than 10 minutes, we will
automatically log the Authorized Customer off.
How does themembershipscript.com use login information?
themembershipscript.com uses login information, including, but not
limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends,
administer the Site, track a user's movement and use, and gather
broad demographic information.

What partners or service providers have access to Personally
Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on
the Site?
themembershipscript.com has entered into and will continue to enter
into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of vendors. Such
vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable
Information on a need to know basis for evaluating Authorized
Customers for service eligibility. Our privacy policy does not cover
their collection or use of this information. Disclosure of Personally
Identifiable Information to comply with law. We will disclose Personally
Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or
subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release
information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information
when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and
Authorized Customers.
How does the Site keep Personally Identifiable Information
secure?
All of our employees are familiar with our security policy and practices.
The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors and Authorized
Customers is only accessible to a limited number of qualified
employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the
information.
 “We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer
details with any 3rd parties”.
While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a
secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to
errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant
that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors
or Authorized Customers for any such occurrences.

How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally
Identifiable Information?
Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update
Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any
inaccuracies by contacting our support team at
http://akhmediagroup.com .
Can a Visitor delete or deactivate Personally Identifiable
Information collected by the Site?
We provide Visitors and Authorized Customers with a mechanism to
delete/deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site's
database by contacting support team at http://akhmediagroup.com .
However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be
impossible to delete a Visitor's entry without retaining some residual
information. An individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable
Information deactivated will have this information functionally deleted,
and we will not sell, transfer, or use Personally Identifiable Information
relating to that individual in any way moving forward.
What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?
We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about
changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site.
However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might
cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or
Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we
will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor
or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure.
Links:

This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when
you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site.
We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked
sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
